阿尔茜 有车辆接近
Arcee, a vehicular form is approaching.
霸天虎吗？
Decepticon?
是我妈…
Huh... Mom...
又来了？
Again?
她担心我
She worries.
嗨 甜心
Hi, honey.
嘿 呃…
Hey, eh...
医院提前下班 所以我想顺便来看看
Finished my shift early at the hospital, so I thought I'd swing by.
很高兴再见到你 医生
Good to see you again, doctor.
阿尔茜
Arcee.
对了 擎天柱在哪儿？
So, where is Optimus?
跟大黄蜂一起执行巡逻任务
On a scouting mission with Bumblebee.
对不起让你扑空了
Sorry to disappoint.
我难得穿一次高跟鞋…
And I wore heels and everything...
妈妈！
Mom!
真奇怪
That's odd.
这种磁通量在任何一个星球上都…极其罕见
This is an extremely unusual magnetic flux... for any planet.
我认识这种磁力特征 声波
I recognize this magnetic signature, Soundwave.
这项霸天虎的发明要是落入敌手 可就太不幸了
And it would be unfortunate to have a Decepticon invention such as this used against us.
我会取回这件武器 威震天陛下
I will secure the weapon, Lord Megatron.
打击？哈！
Breakdown? Hah!
你连区区人类都敌不过 还想对抗汽车人？
If you can be bested by mere humans, what chance do you have against the Autobots?
请允许我戴罪立功 主人
Allow me to redeem myself, master.
我所受到的羞辱 时刻提醒着我 决不再辜负您
What I have lost is a constant reminder that I must never again fail you.
感觉到最后转弯产生的超重了吗？
Hahahahaha... Did you feel the Gs on that last turn?
隔板开车太猛了！
Bulkhead's an animal!
我记得 这里是个秘密俱乐部吧？
Remember when this used to be a secret club house?
呃 别担心 达比小姐 我们系了安全带
Eh, don't worry, Miss Darby. We were wearing seatbelts.
我相信你 拉斐尔
I'm sure you were, Rafael.
嗨 神子！学校里怎么样？
Hi, Miko! How's school going?
什么？你听说什么了？
Why? What you hear?
我们得干活了 杰克
Let's do this thing, Jack.
可是 我刚到 我带了三明治喔
But, I just got here. I brought sandwiches.
妈妈 我真得去帮阿尔茜 测试升级后的追踪系统
Mom. Look, I really need to help Arcee test her upgraded tracking system.
好吧 只是 要小心
Well, just be careful.
没什么可小心的 只不过是例行检查
There's nothing to be careful about. It's a routine diagnostic.
你非得让杰克帮忙吗？
Are you sure you need Jack for that?
啊哦
Eh-oh...
隔板 你得再出趟外勤 调查一个诡异的磁力扰动
Bulkhead, I need you back in the field to investigate an odd magnetic disturbance.
我也要去！
I'll go with!
喔 好好待着 神子
Whoa, stay put, Miko.
你怎么不跟他去？
Why aren't you going with him?
某人觉得不安全
Someone thinks it's not safe.
那杰克跟着阿尔茜就安全了？
But it's safe for Jack to go with Arcee?
妈妈 这完全是两码事
Mom, totally different.
噢 说来听听
Oh, how?
妈妈是为你好 杰克
Mother knows best, Jack.
等等 隔板 我跟你去
Wait up, Bulkhead. I'm going with.
啊 我说什么来着？
Ah, what did I say?
中奖了
Jackpot.
我觉得 你不该独吞…
For me, you shouldn't have...
我没有
I didn't.
我听说虎子出了个败类
I heard a rumour about a rogue 'Con.
要不要我把你五花大绑 捉拿归案？
How about I hogtie you and haul you in?
哼 头脑简单 四肢发达
Huh, the primitive type.
独眼龙看不清目标距离 是吗？
Not much for depth perception any more, are you?
八角怪还有脸说别人！
Or not much for looks anymore.
葬礼真感人
It was a lovely burial.
不好意思 你说什么我听不清
Sorry, can't quite understand you.
那不是针对你 阿尔茜
Don't take it so personal, Arcee.
杰克的母亲只是…有保护欲望
Jack's mother's just... protective.
可她不知道 这几个月我一直在保护她儿子
Well, I protected her son for months before she had a clue.
等她恍然大悟之后…
Suddenly she wakes up to reality and...
又觉得我不够好
I'm not enough.
没错！
No kidding!
我们能不能拒绝她来基地？
Can't we ban her from the base?
神子 你怎么…
Miko, how did you...
呼叫环陆桥
Gonna need a bridge.
等等 别把我送回那个护仔老妈手里
Wait, don't send me back to helicopter mom.
我只是…怀念以前的时光
It's just... I miss the way things were.
取消呼叫 救护车
Strike that, Ratchet.
继续巡逻 还是让她跟着我们吧
It's only recon. She's safe with us.
太好了！
S-weet!
劲爆第七曲 小隔
Crank up track 7, Bulk.
什么第七曲？
Track 7?
你不觉得 这样巡逻太吵了吗？
Do you think that's a little loud for a recon?
侦察兵应该能杀人于无形
A scout should be silent but deadly.
（“杀人于无形”在美国日常生活中用于描述 “响屁不臭，臭屁不响”）
怎么？
What?
（“杀人于无形”在美国日常生活中用于描述 “响屁不臭，臭屁不响”）
Silent but deadly means something completely different on earth.
“杀人于无形”在地球上说的完全是另一回事
小隔 我们继续巡逻吧
Bulk, let's get our recon on.
一向都是我领头的
I always take point.
我知道 可是神子喜欢打前哨 可以看风景
I know, but Miko likes to be at front so she can see.
不管到哪儿 我都是电灯泡
No matter where I turn, I'm the third wheel.
嗯…看来救护车说的磁通量就来自…
Hmm... looks like Ratchet's magnetic flux is coming from...
毒蜘蛛
Airachnid...
还有打击
And Breakdown.
正好是你们俩的宿敌
Both your arch enemies.
他们在窝里斗
And they're mashing it up.
为了抢那个
Over that.
那就是磁力扰动的来源
The source of the magnetic disturbance.
很好 有什么计划？
Alright, what's the plan?
神子 别动 我是认真的
Miko, don't move. I mean it.
阿尔茜 看呐 你带来一个新搭档让我开荤
Arcee. And look, you brought a new partner for me to snuff.
那是隔板
That would be Bulkhead.
谁问你了？
Who asked you?
人间大炮
Launch me.
不 她是我的
No, she's mine.
- 小心那个…\N- 明白
- Watch out for ...\N- Got it.
哇哦 他们俩是绝配
Wow. They're really good together.
嗯 照下来放进纪念册
Ugh... Smack down for the scrap book.
啊…谢谢
Ah... Thank you.
你会用那东西吗？
Do you even know what that does?
那可不是玩具！
It isn't a toy.
嘿！
Hey!
怎么回…
What's going...
哼哼…这个开关是干嘛的？
Hmhmhmm... What's this switch do?
威震天一定喜欢这东西
Megatron's gonna love this.
隔板！
Bulkhead!
虎子们逃跑了
The Cons are getting away.
嘿 我的手机！
Hey, my phone!
粘住了！
It's stuck!
阿尔茜呢？
Where is Arcee?
你干脆跟她结婚好了
Why don't you just marry her?
我就在你后面
I'm right behind you.
哪儿？
Where?
你应该…不用担心后院起火了
Let's just say... she's got your back.
见鬼
Scrap.
我是打击 我需要传送…
Breakdown here. I'm gonna need a bridge...
你们被磁力吸到了一起？
You've been magnetized... together?
呃 他们亲密无间
Uh... They're inseparable.
而且那个磁力装置就要被威震天拿到手了
And the device that did this is on its way to Megatron.
极化拳套 一项看似简单实则恐怖的发明
A polarity gauntlet. A deceptively simple but diabolical creation.
你到底能不能把我们分开 救护车
Just tell me you can unhitch us, Ratchet.
从目前的引力状况来看 可能只是残余的…磁力作用
It may simply be a residual magnetic charge, providing your current attraction.
他们俩不仅仅是吸引！
They are not attracted to each other.
恐怕抵消这个作用的最佳方案 是夺回拳套
But I'm afraid retrieving the gauntlet is our surest bet for reversing its effect.
威震天一旦拿到了这个拳套…
Once Megatron gets his hands on the gauntlet...
肯定不会只用它 在冰箱上贴便签和家庭照片
He'll use it for a whole lot more than attaching notes and family photos to the fridge.
杰克？我没听明白
Jack? I'm not following.
女士 我们是用合金铸造的
Madam, we are forged of metal alloy.
如果威震天按动开关就能把我们击退 我们可能再也没机会打败他了
If Megatron could repel us with a flick of the switch, we might never again have another shot at him.
瞬间力场
Instant force field.
更不用说 他可以用那东西把我们压成一堆废铁
Worse yet, he might use it to meld us all into a scrap pile.
好消息是 那个拳套还没走远
The good news is the gauntlet hasn't travelled far.
我强烈建议你们追上去
I would strongly advise pursuit.
四个轮子 很快就到了
We can catch up fast on wheels.
喔 喔 喔！你想把我折成两半吗？
Whoa, whoa, whoa! And snap me in half?
哦 对…
Right...
太棒了！
S-weet!
我来领头
I'll take point.
这次不行 小鬼
Not this time, kid.
什么？可是你说过…
What? But you said...
当时是巡逻 现在是战斗
That was recon. This is war.
我不能用你的安全冒险 你今天的历险到此为止
I'm not risking your well-being just so you can hit your daily adrenaline quota.
救护车 神子需要环陆桥
Ratchet, Miko needs a bridge.
就来
Coming up.
呃！杰克的妈妈就够烦人了 可你说话跟她一样！
Ugh! You think Jack's mom's bad? You sound just like her.
关心孩子有什么不对吗？
Is that such a bad thing?
我去接她
I'm gonna go for her.
很称手嘛！
It fits!
你知道 女孩总是嫌首饰不够多
You know, a girl can never have too many accessaries.
你也当过霸天虎 我们可以一起把礼物献给威震天
You were a Decepticon once. We can bring the prize to Megatron together.
让我回到那个狼窝？我出来单干 是因为我不喜欢与人分享
Go back to that boys' club? I struck out on my own because I don't like to share.
这东西正好能让轮子和虎子都离我远点儿
This will provide the perfect repellent against 'Bots and 'Cons alike.
我的后脑勺以前从没长过眼睛
Never had eyes in the back of my head before
现在连后背都有枪了
or blasters to cover my rear.
你也有了坚强的后盾
And you get a built-in shield.
隔板 你不会也觉得我很像琼吧？
Bulkhead, you don't really think I sound like June, do you?
呃…
Er...
她是过度保护
She's over protective.
我只是…一般保护
I'm just... protective.
完全不同…
Totally different...
接近拳套了
The gauntlet's close.
我猜 阿尔茜随后就到
I assume Arcee isn't far behind.
可以这么说
You might say that.
把手举起来 转过身去
Blast your hands in the air and turn around.
遵命…
Whatever you say...
停火协议还有效吗 肌肉男？
Still up for a truce, muscles?
我只不过是更恨隔板罢了
Only because I hate Bulkhead more than I hate you.
噢…怎么？
Oh... What?
隔板 你能站着别动吗？
Bulkhead, would you stay still?
我的错
My bad.
喔
Whoa...
需要帮手吗？
Need a hand?
不 她是我的！
No, she's mine!
两个轮子 一起送命
Two Bots. One stump.
小隔 低头！
Bulk, duck!
隔板…起…来！
Bulkhead... Get... up!
骨瘦如柴
Pins like a bug.
当然了 我有个一劳永逸的办法让你解脱
Of course I can think of one permanent way out of your predicament.
我攻上盘
I'll take topside.
哈！
Hah!
我自由了
I'm free.
想跳个舞吗？
Wanna dance?
你不是我喜欢的类型
You're not my type.
见鬼
Scrap.
让男生们自己玩吧
Let's leave the boys to themselves.
我们两个私下里谈谈
That would be the upclose and personal setting.
一条腿废了 还有五条陪你玩儿
One hand tied, five more to play with.
质量不过关 再多也没用
Quality, not quantity.
同性相斥
Opposite do not attract.
我们碰不到金属物体
We can't touch metal.
我们被极化了
We are polarized.
我总是见好就收
Always leave on the high note.
隔板 拳套！
Bulkhead, the gauntlet!
把他们解决掉吧
Let's finish this.
不怕再次合体吗？
And risk becoming twins again?
是个纪念品 不过…
Souvenir, but...
不建议在室内使用
We don't advise indoor use.
哎哟 他们都开始一唱一和了
Eyu... They even finish each other's sentences.
神子 看看这个――几道新伤
Miko, check it out-- new battle scars.
阿尔茜 嘿…
Arcee, hey...
小孩子别插嘴
Let the adults talk.
阿尔茜 我想我应该向你道歉
Arcee, I think I owe you an apology.
是吗？
You do?
我经常担心…尤其是觉得力不从心的时候
I worry... especially when I feel like I can't control things--
照顾一个处在青春期的孩子 太操心了
which, with a teenager, is all the time.
杰克和我一直很亲近
Jack and I have always been close.
特别是他父亲离开之后…
Especially, after his dad left. And...
我想我只是…很难一下子接受生活的变化
I guess it's just... hard to accept that all that's changing.
我也知道 生活迟早要改变 只是…
I mean I knew it would someday, but...
你不是我想象的那种 让杰克鬼迷心窍的女孩
you're not quite the type of girl I thought Jack would be ditching me for.
我想我们都有点过于留恋从前的时光
I think we've all been a little guilty of staying attached to the way things were.
打击 你竟敢空手回来见我？！
Breakdown, you dare to return empty-handed?!
不 主人
No, Master.
毒蜘蛛…久违了
Airachnid... it has been some time.
威震天陛下…说什么好呢？很高兴能归队
Lord Megatron... what can I say? It's good to be back.